¿Qué tan romántico?
And hot.
That's hot, okay?
Hey, Gina.
Gina.
What's up with you?
No time for romance.
Oh, no time
for romance, really?
Nice.
No time for romance.
No time for living.
No time for nothing.
You know what?
You need to forget this
bloody sucker Spencer
and start living
your own life.
It's for you.
Spencer is not a bloodsucker.
Oh, really?
And who is he?
A werewolf?
No.
He's just a man who
wanted me to give him
a child.
Then I found out that I can't,
so I have no right
to take away his future.
Long story short, he's an ex.
I'm so sorry,
but prince charming
gave you his card
and code.
Will you confess
who's behind all these goodies?
Trust me.
Comparing to that bloodsucker,
Spencer is just a mosquito.
How intriguing.
Red flags are not intriguing.
No, no, no.
Oh my gosh.